Welcome to Psyche Awakens, a show in the panel verse where tarot, truth and raw conversation meet.
We explore boldly, we disagree intelligently and we protect the circle.
Here's how we roll.
House rules.
Debate ideas, not people.
No doxing, slander, hate or threats, ever.
Bring receipts, claims need sources or timestamps, no rumour relays, signal discipline, mix muted
and less called, no spam, no derail, the mods are the guardians, warning time out, batten,
no negotiations mid-show.
This is Psyche's channel, Psyche's Rules.
He keeps it safe, sharp and on topic.
Use common sense and be respectful to everyone and you will be fine.
Contribute or be entertained welcome if you're here to sow chaos hang out. There's a place for you here, too
Now welcome your host psyche. See ya storyteller and your host eat truth first shadow second
Let's get into it
Yeah, I tried I did try times that she'd go one-on-one. I don't know maybe Mr.
She said but no she wasn't planning on doing that. She was gonna have all five people up there
Sam and Eldo, I mean, what the fuck? Isn't she ridiculous? Oh, no conditions
All I said is that can we go one-on-one and then not
Someone you know someone sends money to clap me in the middle of my sentence not to clap me which happened on salmon the last three times
Which happens on summer's channel so and then she is clapping she clap my friend for five dollars, right?
Talk about you know. Oh my god. I'm my desperation. Just one person offended me one time. She kicks him off
for five dollars, right?
I never clapped anyone for five dollars,
except it was like, you know, five dollars a minute,
or five dollars for five minutes or something like that.
Yeah, it's ridiculous.
It's ridiculous, it's stupid.
It's like, I tried.
Guys, I tried, I did try.
I thought I was live, I was live.
And then I ended because I thought she was gonna
do a one-on-one with me.
You know, like a lot of people in chat
would like to see that.
Yeah.
Even if it's like just even if like she can she can take it as a friendship or she can take it as
Content like whatever she wants to take it as either way. It's a win-win
But no she can't do that
It would be clipped for sure and it would be like a lot better of a clip than yeah, I tried
Yeah
What can I do what can I do
I just don't understand why she can't talk to me without other people there like she needs like the support like she like
And also she used to put conditions on me all the time. Oh my gosh, you know
I'm I'm gonna I'm never coming back here again. Let's you do this unless you do this. That's what she'd always say, right?
She told me to kick people up I know she you know she's a she's a coward just coward
You can't talk that's all he had was two conditions
We do it one-on-one
And no one kicks me off like from the audience, you know,
cause a lot of people will probably try and stuff, right?
So, yeah.
Yeah, go ahead and talk about KK Salmon.
Like that's so interesting.
KK is a nice person.
Salmon's a nice person.
Whatever, it's not that interesting to me.
I don't understand the whole KK Salmon stuff.
But who, I mean, really, I mean, go talk about that.
Just stop using me for content though because when I went over there, you're all talking about me. You name the stream referencing me
I'm doing it to myself. Okay, but what I tried but I was trying I was keep trying I
Thought it was worth maybe say salvaging a relationship, but it's not to her
And it's like, it's not like I'm just like some shmo off the chat.
It's like, I'm also a contact, oh, and then she's like, oh, and then person's in there.
So, oh my God, you know, I made 40 subscribers last week.
It's like, whatever.
It's like, I don't have the hugest thing, but sometimes it levels out and so, whatever.
So that's it.
I've come on very calm.
Watch back yesterday's thing, watch the trip, kick things.
You can just see, I just get bulldozed.
It's not fair.
So if I set a condition for like 10 minutes,
what is it?
She's on for like 12 hours at a time.
What's 10 minutes to like not have a bunch of like,
you know, people like echoing in the background.
I don't know.
I guess not worth it.
I'm not worth it to her.
She's not worth it to me.
You're right, charisma.
I give up.
I just give up on that.
That is just one, that is just one rabbit hole
you don't want to go down.
It's just fucking ridiculous.
Regondandiculous.
Nihon Priestess.
Right?
Support Alexander Mayer's please.
That's a real one.
I saw that.
I have to step away.
Here for more support
Bye, MQO.
Probably gypsy. You don't even want to. I've heard a lot of bulls bread. How about
Oh, cry me out.
You run to Bita, you run to Bita to tell.
Oh, Bita, he's good, he's talking about, he's gonna show.
Like, what the fuck?
I know that was you.
Oh.
What, is it reasonable to ask for a one-on-one?
I don't know.
No, run to Bita, run to Bita.
Go to Bita's, she'll give you a platform.
Oh, I introduced you, that's what's annoying.
You bring up Emma and clumsy. How about like those are my relationships to worry about how about you stay out of what that right?
You don't know what happened in those relationships.
Ugh. I
Had you fucking promote it on my new website.
You're just done with the drama. Well, you're in the middle of it now because you come in saying, oh, you're doing this to your old friends.
I'm so sick of people saying that. They're obviously not my friends.
You focus on you and I never did anything wrong to you. I never did. What did I do wrong to you for you to like just like go
Against me like that. I
Don't know nothing
Thought we were friends
Right well, it was a surprise the website's not up yet. I was gonna like show you but yeah, and yeah, I'm kidding you
Well, I'll be sure to take you off
All it was to do was to promote you. All it was to do was to try to help.
I didn't try to help you, I didn't introduce you guys.
Plus, I don't forget what you did, but you got...
You tried to get me clipped on thinking that?
What are you talking about, you nut?
You're just nuts, I'm about to block you in the shed.
What the fuck so silly
So silly and I remember when when the whole clumsy thing happened
Well, I was blocked immediately in your chat and you left my discord, right over the clumsy
I mean what without about yeah, I don't know. What did I do? I still don't know
I still don't know and I didn't try to get you clipped on anything
You were on her damn show and trip kick clicks you do you think I I controlled trip kick?
No
You think
See these are called turncoats and they're gonna say oh gypsy was such a good friend to you. Oh, yeah
Does she look did you hear me out that you say hey, what's going on? No, she always just runs to beat
Oh, you know, it's like girls club. It's gonna be girls club. I'm wrong cuz I'm a male, right I
Got your name wrong. Well, I'm sorry. So you have gypsy tarot
Your name is not able to be tagged because you have some kind of setting on what the fuck
No time if she doesn't she doesn't time she doesn't you see what yeah, do you see look these are these are my friends
These are my friends. Oh, you're giving up all your old friends. Oh
Tired of that narrative these are people that betrayed me betrayers
No, she's too cowardly trust me. She's too cowardly. I'll get up at the link down if some if she comes up
I'll do one-on-one. I will but she's not going to
Whatever what what did I do gypsy? What did I do what personal stuff what personal stuff crush you?
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what you're talking about. I have no idea
You're just you drink the Kool-Aid. It's okay. It's okay. Everyone does everyone like a lot of people do
I'm not really surprised. Well, if it's not about emmer clumsy, why do you bring that up first?
You said emmer emmer clumsy. I know J-dog
People are just hurt you don't think they'll betray me on purpose what it's like
Look at all the people that are over there as her mods that we used to be my mods
There's but hurt that I unmodded them or did something right?
There's no you don't come at me kindly you come at me yelling at me, okay?
I'm self-deflecting what what do you want me to say Teresa? What do you want me to say?
I was with you from the beginning. I was with you from the beginning, okay before any of this
I brought you into the world, okay?
Yeah, I don't think any credit for it. You say golly, but it's fine
Wow
Maybe she had stuff going on in her life. Who are you talking about Samantha like what?
She's playing I'm being blamed for everything. I mean blame for everything
You needed you I needed you the most one year ago, so you don't need me anymore
That's fine. Talk about a stepping stone. You know is yeah you like a
No, no, I
Was there I was there. I've always been here. I've been right here, right?
You have privately DME to talk to a good friend
Nope, nope, I wasn't there
Well, how wasn't I there I you wrote that message I wrote you back you haven't written me a message since
Yeah, I asked you to go to that chat. Did you defend me? No. Did you say one word in defense of me? No, not one word
It's fine. It's fine. I just know what to expect now
Now I know what to expect home. What is that song? What is the song?
What is the song now I know what to expect
Song I
Do know what to expect now here. This is my song
Through stones at my name, slender painted on the wall.
Ducks my life, laughed out loud.
Tried to make me small, packages of spite at my door.
Phone calls in the night, gaslit flames, bad cat dad.
But I'm still here to fight.
Let them whisper, let them spin.
the truth begins every shadow fades away I'm busy Teresa I have proof too this is
I was there.
I've been there.
Talking to you after- Oh, because you blocked me on discord and left my discord and wrote a completely mean message.
I'll share the message.
Can I share the message?
It's a terrible thing.
me now too. Hey Alex I remember the song where it says I know what to expect it's called uh
it's the uh what is it called it's called um
now I know what to oh it's yeah it's my freaking taxi song troll side of the panel
by the way I write these songs troll side of the panel
Twisting the stories and working on the mod status whatever. Oh
God
It's such bullshit
Such bullshit never be on my side never be on my side
Turn on me on the dime
It's okay
Now I know what to expect
Hey, babe
Hi, baby, baby, baby. I don't see it
Trollside of the panel. That's it called
I'll be right there
Now I'm gonna be it. Oh everybody turn on everybody
Everybody turn on me
Ah, we're back.
Gotta be my laundry out.
i thought that i could win but the chat just sighed won't you banish me they said i wasn't reasonable
nothing was debatable with me i tried to flood and pull one over all the mods who fed me but what
Go to your side, I'm gonna have a fight.
Can I work it out with anybody?
No.
Ready to lose the hat and regrow the hair?
Let's see posted on her community page. Let's have a look. Let's have a look
Let's go have a look at what I did. Let's see the the horrible things I did on Teresa's community page
Oh, and I oh and I did something wrong because I tagged the wrong traveling gypsy because I can't couldn't she doesn't have her name set up in the
Tagging okay fine. Let's just share it. Let's share
Right there one second. Let's go to Teresa's community page and have a look at her receipts. Let's see
I mean guys, I'm gonna look really bad right now. Let me see how bad I'm gonna look
Let me see my this is gonna be really embarrassing. I'm sure I traveling gypsy
Okay, let's see okay on YouTube, okay
Yeah, there's what I mean, that's the biggest thing I did. Oh, I tagged the wrong person. It's called an accident
I mean, it's I don't know. It's getting too dumb for me. There's gonna be stupid, but let's see the receipts
I want to see how what a bad person I am
Let's have a look my traveling gypsy tarot and let's go to community page and I will share the screen
post
Okay, here we go. Okay. Okay. Well what I see is
Her okay, well, okay, so she's sharing messages. Let me share
Let's see try to look out for you
But you don't want to listen or care for my opinion
My problem with you is your behavior and how you have been treating your friends
I made my own decision based on what I saw with my own eyes
You used to be there, but I always am here for you if that makes sense. Love you. Okay. Um, I don't know
I don't know about that
Okay, well, let's go to the real thing.
Let me see.
I need to open my Discord and have a look.
Let's go to the full message,
because if she wants to share messages,
you can share messages.
Let's have a look, Discord.
This is another time you hurt me.
Oh, wow.
I don't see anything I said that hurt you,
but let me see.
Let's see. Was this when you like unmodded me and left my discord? Let me see. I'll read the message. I'm not gonna show it
I'll just read it. Let's see. Let me see
Go back up to it
Okay, I said
Blocked me didn't ask me about it first misunderstanding as usual. I wish you the best
Here's what she said. I saw your live and I know you deleted it
How dare you put words in my mouth keep my name out of your mouth
I've always tried to look out for you
But you don't want to listen to me or care for my opinion my problem with you is your behavior and how you have been treating your friends
I made my own decision based on what I saw with my own eyes
Used to be a tarot channel and you've changed things up and not in a healthy way
You left Emma's discord and then
went on your live and got nasty. I blocked you because of your behavior in Emma's live chat
and her discord and your behavior looks creepy and obsessive. You vent all your personal problems
and talk about people on your live stream. You diss them one minute but apologize for your actions.
You have no respect for other people's boundaries. You expect people to forgive your actions knowing
I was drunk as an excuse a lot. Keep your drama on your channel. Don't bring it on other people's
channels. I'm trying to protect my channel and I've got enough going on in my life.
To be having this affect my online life. My discord is very private and for tarot streamers
I want to keep it a safe and drama-free environment. I talked to you
but I but I
Talked to you, but let me see
Where to go, but we'll tell you your stream about it and I'm not about it
I didn't wish to size by my own best of wishes keep leave me out of it. I don't see I love you there and
then
Then you said, how are you doing? I have a question. Have I ever done anything wrong or lied to you about anything?
I said, no, I don't feel that way
I did have my feelings hurt a little bit when you muted me in your chat and left my discord, but we made up
About it lots of third-party drama in my life this year has been exhausting and it's with a lot of people
She goes I lurk on your stream all the time when you go live and well the people in chat who talk about Janet and her taking
Wrenches and what they say is true. I know that it's none of my business, but it's you're on your channel
I just wanted to let you know
On because what they say about her is correct to be careful as I'd appreciate it. Thanks for letting me know
Anyway, I mean, I don't know. I don't know you just like kind of like made it look different than it was. I don't know anyway
You're protecting your heart from me. Oh, what did I do to you? You said it was about Emma
You said it was about Emma's discord, right? What did I do to you?
Why is it about Emma and what it was? I mean, it's like Emma and clumsy. You didn't even like those people
I mean, geez, maybe you like clumsy, but you certainly didn't like Emma, but anyway
I'm not trying to use content. I'm just saying it's like this is like right
You understand you're being used Teresa, not by me I
Said and I'll show you the well read the latest thing the latest thing was when I said they're having a live about me
I'm getting stuff sent to my house
People looking for scrap metal and stuff, right? Right? I
Didn't do shit to you like I didn't
But you're like going against me for no reason because you just choose sides and you're like I don't choose sides
Would I ask you I said I?
Say criminal harassment door knocks people looking for scrap metal
To fertilizer an unpaid pizza sent to my house all day and then I show the brand because the guy allied master computer was on that
Did I mentioned beta or did I say go over there? No?
I just put the link to bronze birds chat, and you're like what is this?
I said psyche haters club. It's meeting now. You said you're making class. Okay. You're like, so why would I go there?
I said maybe to have my back. You're like, oh, I'm on a break. Okay. That's what that's what it is
But you didn't have my back. I
Know you're a rakey club, but you did go in there and you said hi, but
You know, I would have totally understood I was letting everybody know but you had enough time to talk to beta about it and say
You know, he's asking me to go defend him or something like that because she's like three or four people told me that and
But how many people did I tell three or four people?
This is how psyche treats all those friends. Yeah, like well, you're not my friend BG. So why don't you stay the fuck out of it?
Okay, okay, but did you see what was going on because the whole thing was about me. It says psyche asleep tarot
It's okay. I know you're already Ricky clouds. You're gonna check it out later. You get the replay the thing was
That was all slander. You should see what they talk about me, you know, I
Know you didn't tell anyone and I don't I didn't I didn't say I had a problem with you. Well
Who could it have been let me think
Because beat is like everyone's saying have my back the only person I said something about having my back was to you
And so I don't know how she would know that but yeah, maybe I'm wrong
This is how I treat all my friends right right bronze or right are you my friend BG no
Yeah, go pick up go pick up Q who maces homeless people that's fine, right you can
I know I expect too much from people I do
Just like you're in here defending beta right now having betas back saying oh look how you treat your friends
Look how you treated Emma and clumsy, right?
It's okay if no one listens at least if I had one person saying one nice thing about me that I knew
Right, it's okay. It's okay. I don't expect it. I don't expect it. No one's no one's gonna defend me
I am the piece of garbage, right? I'm dirty covered in fleas and ticks and bed bugs and lice and
Look at the cards predicted this. Yeah, I'm just like I'm just like, you know, you should hear what they say about me
I would never let anybody say that about you. Oh
God all day every day
Thank you H
You didn't Teresa you came in saying what is your what did you came in saying you came in saying?
Well, you have hurt a lot of your of our old friends
That sounds like
I meant falls right away, that's like so I'm gonna be on defensive especially
You were just over there and Vitas, you know, you don't don't join my panel anymore. You just joined hers
Oh sweetheart, you know, it's like, I am attacked, that's okay, it's okay.
I get upset and I overreact and I feel triggered and I get hurt because
All I wanted to get all I wanted to do is have 10 minutes with Bita to talk to her if she wanted to
Try to salvage the friendship because the last three times I've been on
She has been
Attacking me and I mean have to has has to have four or five people on yelling at me
And then the last time they said okay
Well, everyone will mute and nobody muted and people were talking over me and so I left and then they're like well
You ran I didn't run. It's not a fair fight and I don't want to fight. I was trying to have a conversation
She still won't have the conversation and it's like and I asked for that condition
I mean she used to tell me kick this person out of here
Talk about you and me that's what see that's exactly how it should be
It's like every day, you know how much I woke up this morning
People banging on my door this guy and his granddaughter looking for scrap metal
You then it happens again, then it happens again, then it happens again
They have that guy on the show. It's okay Teresa and I apologize if I overreacted and sorry
Maybe I misunderstood but it's like
You know my feelings are hurt too and everyone's acting like I'm just this hurtful mean person and I'm not it's like I get pushed
into a corner and
I get upset and it's like, and I'm sorry if I wasn't there for you when you needed me, but I'm here
I mean, it's like I always try to take your calls or call you back or write back. I always will have you on panel. I
Know and well, actually, they're not they're not bad people. They're nice people some of the people I talked to are really nice
I'm sorry overreacted. I'm just in bad mood about like, you know, Bita won't talk to me for five minutes
Not even a minute
YouTube world's not for you, but we're in you're in it Teresa, and I'm sorry if I brought you too far into this
Can the drama community by introducing you to her?
I mean, it's like, you know, she's talking about Chona. She's like, oh your Chona just bought you all your subscriptions or whatever
Understand with Chona, right? She understands. You know, you know how wonderful Chona is?
She's she's like now. She's bad-mouthing Chona, right?
The sweetest like the sweetest lady
I said, Jonah, help me get my channel started, not you, Vita.
I had over a thousand people in my chat and she's like,
oh, you just, she bought all the people.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Teresa, you were there.
You were in my early lives, right?
There were lots of people among them.
I had at least like 10 people in my very early lives.
When you do like live streams, people can come in and stuff.
And they don't pay for the pizza though.
And so it's not pizza, it's just an unpaid pizza
that I'm expected to pay for.
And so I have to send the disappointed Mexican pizza lady
away and stuff.
Okay, I'm sorry.
What kind of pizza?
I like a nice Brooklyn style.
Yeah, focus on your Reiki, Teresa.
Maybe I'm too much for people or anything.
I'm a marketer.
Like I can I can show you what I was, you know, it's okay
Do I have it up? Let me see if I do. I'll show you then you can I'll take I'll take you off
If you want to be off of it, but if you don't want to be then I I don't know this was to help people
So I have the psyche verse, right?
It's psycheverse.org. It's not done. It's still in the process
This is what I'm working on. You can see if it's a piece of junk that you don't want to be associated with or whatever
But hold on
This was like I was so excited to show you as a surprise and stuff like that
It wasn't trying to use you or anything or like, you know, you use your for cloud
It was like I want to help you. Okay, but here's what it was. So this is the website I've been working on
Do you see it psyche burst?
Okay, and then I have traveling gypsy tarot there right it tells when you're on and offline
It's like I have summer up there. I have you know, Alexandra mayors. I have my site, you know
It tells when people are alive
That's all it does. That's all it's and I was like, you know
Just to be nice
Okay, but I made sure that you were on there, you know, one of the first people I had other people there, right?
But that's what it was. I mean, it's like it's okay if you don't want to be associated. I was it was like
Gosh, I've had surprises for people and like
Most people that had surprises for turn on me before I even got to show them and stuff
But yeah, that's what it was. It's like just like, you know a little website with like people that I like listed and stuff
That's all it was it wasn't like trying to
To the ice I love you. I don't know it's like and it's like it hurts people
I love turn on me for her again and again and again. They got HK Memphis. They got sweepy all these people
They're constantly harassing with the biscuit song. Look at look at her thing. Oh biscuit queen
What is it? Is it about something other than trying to fuck with me?
I don't think so because that's a 14 year old meme that she begged me to play on my show and I was like now
Then I write a biscuit song
Called beat his biscuits, and it's like oh, that's harassing. It's a good. It was a good nature thing. I love you Goddy. I'll Goddy. I love you, too
I don't know I
Get tired I get tired
It's like it's called like a hate
Let's see people just hate it's like I get tired of just like all the hate
Okay
Well, I'm gonna be happy to post, you know post you on my community board with that
You know this websites for basically about the streamer version stuff like that or like the people that have YouTube shows
And so that's why I have your channel up, but
You want to promote your Reiki? I'm happy to put your thing up on the thing. I think you're a good person
I think that it's like
Beta has turned you against me. Okay
Well, I know but it's separate so I'll uh
Yeah, this is yeah, this is the this is the video. I made Teresa about that gathering. Okay
It is about what it is at least it's to annoy me because it's like why is it taking such a life of my own?
Well, I'm slow. What is it about explain it? Everyone keeps asking. What is that about?
You know, we weren't here that night. Okay. Okay. Well, Teresa, whatever like whatever you want
I will promote you but here's the here's a song about the haters club
Christine's mad about crystal, Tony's just full of it.
Braun's chicken struts around, but it's looking like a lunatic.
Sweet pea is gone sour, beet has bitter Betty again.
Welcome to the Psyche Hater's Club
Where the gel is gathered up
Begging for attention, thirsty and stuck
One club I'm happy, I'm not part of
Go hate yourselves
Yeah, go hate yourselves
Bronze chicken pluck though
those feathers, toss it in the pan
Welcome to the psyche haters club where the jelly
Okay, I'm sorry, now my camera keeps fucking up, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Josh, I'm under a lot of stress right now.
Last five days, like five or six days,
I've been every day people coming to collect
Scrap metal. It's not the only way Theresa. I'm on discord. You can always message me there
You can try to call me from there. I can't I can't talk through my tablet
I have to go on my computer and do it so you have to like give me a like a little heads up about it
You can also talk to me on my panel
I'm gonna put my link up if you'd like to come have a nice chat with me since nobody else will like you know like
since I
Know Jamie, but it's like you understand
I can't even like get a good night's sleep right now.
Okay?
I got, and nobody cares, nobody cares.
Nobody cares what I go through.
Like, you know, it's like, yeah, this is, that's the evil eye.
I'm under a lot of stress.
Trying to like run the show, having my tarot business,
constantly slander, hold on.
I got you, Teresa, one sec.
Okay, I'm sorry if my camera is not coming on. I'm sorry. Yeah
Hello
Hi
so I
um a long time ago I
Got advised to do that. I didn't want to
Because I don't know what was going on in your chat at the time because they were looking at your chat
Like hell walker and everybody and they're like you got to be careful because like this has to be good vibes only and shit like that
So I apologize for that. I did I did undo it
But I haven't honestly been going live for a long time
Just because I've been doing self healing and stuff like that
But yeah, I tried to reach out a few times when I was going through stuff. I'm happy. We're talking now
Yeah, well, I've been I've been here and I know but I've tried to DM you a few times
I just because like your discord and also I'm I guess Jamie said it's cleaned up since then or
something like that that's why I'm not on your discord because a lot of I've heard a lot of
Oh, what was it? There was nude nude pictures or something somebody was trying to yeah
Or something like that. Yeah blade put on hi Rana's nudes and then deleted them
I kicked him out of the discord and
You know the discord did get taken over by like trolls too at one time. Yeah, the distort is basically dead. I don't
I haven't posted on discord forever. I just checked the messages there once in a while
So i'm sorry if I didn't like you know stay on top of it
But hopefully you have I know you got lots of shit going on too
I don't think i've never stopped worrying about you because like we've known each other
Holy shit over three years
Think about it adan wolfshadow is where we met. Yeah
I love you. Yeah a long time and uh
You know, and I really do support you and I love you and it's like I it's just like but I have so many people turning on me
So many people and it's like so if I jump to conclusions and get upset and stuff like that. No, I get it and I understand that too. I was just like
Always been worried that like
Because I've had my because some I thought were good friends crushed me and so I've always like second-guessing things now
That's why I was like when I was going through all that. I tried to reach out to you. I needed a good friend to talk
I'm gonna cry
I'm sorry Teresa. I'm sorry, and I'm sorry I snapped at you and
Don't cry. Don't cry sweetie. Hey with Jamie's Cowboys is coming up. So this should make you feel better
You mind if Jamie Cowboys comes up?
Um, no, I don't mind, but I just like it you and me though at the same time because okay mind you we can do our personal private
Tots, but she she she hung up she hung up, okay, but um because this is more private to you as well
But you know and I love your can I you know, and I'm really sorry about your cat
You know, it's like I love that cat and you know
He's a I'm sorry, you know, and I think I
Hopefully was there to give you condolence about that too. No, you weren't I was I was in this chat and you said that's when you announced it
And I said I'm so sorry. I do remember that I was you know, it's oh because I did a live
Memorial well, you know, I was blocked in your chat. I'm not exactly sure
No, you know, you're not you haven't been for a long time
I haven't been no, but I said I saw you on beat us and that's when you that's when you announced it
And that's when I remember. Oh talking to you about it, but okay, no, you're not blocked. You're not blocked
Okay, well, I just like, you know, I have over 2,000 subscriptions and so you don't always come up on live, but yeah
I get that because I'm not in the algorithm and honestly
I hardly go live anymore just because like there's a lot of tarot readers out there and
And I want to focus on doing one-on-one private rickie sessions
Yeah, because I can do the long distance now, but I don't want to do it on youtube
Yeah, because like, you know with all that energy coming in you got to really protect and sacred, right?
Yeah
It's a lot and uh, I don't know if you know what's been going on with me and beta and all this stuff
But it's like she's just been she's been going on me hard saying oh, you know
You're not a good tarot. She beat was but one point saying that she was a better tarot
Or she didn't mean no tarot right she does the her own and I never disparage her way of doing
The readings and anything she I loved when she did readings. She hasn't done one for me for a long long time
Yeah
And like what I honestly think I didn't know what's going on
What I honestly think is that you guys do need to talk one-on-one not on panel or anything out
Because she needs to have her own mind
After she's refuses. She's like, I'm not talking to you on the phone
I'm not talking like and so there's a pot
So the only way I can talk is on our panel and she's having four or five people against me
Oh, you're just and then and she insists on it. I just was over there trying to talk one-on-one. Yeah, I know
I didn't know I wasn't aware of that that that was the only way to get a hold of her
I know you have her number. I have her number
I have her number, but she said she asked her if I can call her yesterday and she said no
She doesn't want to talk to me like that and so I text message. She keeps reading my text messages on the thing
You know, she's really
Said terrible things about me. I'm just about dick. I'm just clout chasing
She made me all this stuff and now she's saying oh
Well, chona made me because you know chona bought all my subscribers which is not true
And you know chona is a great person. I don't want her being dragged into the middle of this either
You know, um, but she's disparaging chona who like also wanted to help her and stuff like that
And I know chonas helped you know, I don't know chona helped me a lot and so
you know starting a channel is not an easy thing and uh, you know getting to like the
I don't know. It's like now she has a problem with everything. Everything. I can't do anything, right, right?
Everything is like my fault and it's like I turned against all my friends and whatever
These people
FKC whatever yeah, I was on beta's panel for a minute
because I thought psych was gonna come up because I want to try and make peace between those two at the same time and
see what the hell
But I'm over here and I'm you know like go after yourself
Well, I mean it's like people have been over there saying hey, let him let it talk one-on-one talk for ten minutes
She can't give me ten minutes
She can't give me one oh and you do you see like there's something wrong with that because it's like it was
I'm not just like some random person in the chat, you know
It's not Vita's fault. She's surrounded by snakes. Yeah, I know she is too. I know she is and yeah, Christine over there saying
Oh, well, Eldo you watch over her. It's like it feels like she's being handled
No, I think what she meant by that I was there that you wouldn't like because Vita is sensitive
We both know that I think it was more like protect her feelings not to like
I'm not gonna know you know what I mean. It was nothing really jumping like attack you or anything
For her safety her security, I guess. Yeah, someone weird like that. Yeah, but it's like I'm not there to attack her
I've been trying to make peace for a long time and I've been like begging and it's like I've been trying she's not been trying
I've been trying
That's what's like upsetting is like I put so much effort into it since May
I've been like she started getting mad at me in May and it's been the same thing the only time we ever got to talk was when
You know on her show and stuff or like oh, we talked one-on-one on the phone
And we always got along on the phone, but then the same day I go to her panel and she's like really been mean
I don't know. She has a mean side. I don't know if you saw the black widow stuff that I tried to tag you in
Where it's like she's I mean there's a million trip kick
Things that you can go see where you can see how she talks about me. It's not nice
It's actually like pretty cruel and it's like
You know, I don't know if you've seen it but it's like she's been really mean to me and I have no I try and stay
I'm trying to stay out of it as much as possible
But I've been learning a lot of few things as well at the same time
and
It's just shocking because like it's just like
Just tired of you know fake friends and stuff like that. I've been hurt way too many times to have my
genuine heart
Yeah, you know I haven't been a fake friend and sometimes I have been very busy
You know like running this channel and sometimes I maybe have neglected some relationships
But I've always had the door open and especially I've had the door open for people want to come back and say hey
I'm like I'm sorry to me because I've already been over everybody's channel saying I'm sorry and
forgive me, and if I did something wrong. I used to drink a lot more. And sometimes when I drank, I would say stupid things, you know, I admit that, but I drink a lot less now. And it's like, I noticed that actually, I was going to say I'm very proud of you for that.
Yeah. And well, thank you. And, but especially like just running a show, it's like, so I don't know. My door is open. And I'm not a perfect person, right? No one is. But it's like, I don't deserve
But I've been getting and it's like really it's like and then it's like
All these third-party things. It's like why is all these people getting involved in my my friendship
Like what why can't it be like me and the person just like it is now and like you know and Jamie was like
You know, I would have like well Jamie is like, you know
She hardly ever comes up and stuff like that and I do want to talk to her too
But I'll talk to her one-on-one and it but yeah, it's like I'm happy to have one-on-one if you prefer and stuff
And and anybody I'll talk one-on-one. I don't understand why she can't just talk to me one-on-one
So it's like obviously she needs like
A posse and like why why is it fair? What then can I have one person up there, too?
That that is on my side, too
if she's gonna do that
Literally four to five people against one person and literally me not able to speak like they just scream over me
Like yeah, I get that I get that that's why I was like
Wanted to stay up there and waiting for you, too
But I am out. I'm actually over time at work right now
You're you're you know Trisa you've been a good friend to me. I'm sorry if I snapped it to you
No, you're good. You're good because I snapped at you two at the same time, but okay, that's what we do
We're good. We're good. Okay. We're good. I'm so I'm so and I'm sorry
And so you if you want to talk privately, you know
I'll make sure you have my phone number my private phone number and you can call me anytime and it's like and if I
If I don't answer, I will get back to you.
And I'm sorry if I wasn't there.
And I know you've been going through tough things too.
And I regret if I haven't been there all the time.
And yeah, you are an amazing person.
I know you have a lot of people that love you here
and people that today were trying to calm me down
so I can take a breath.
And I just say, you know, I'm not going to do that.
You know, I don't I never meant any harm to you. I only mean good for you
I only want good things for you, you know, because I think you're a great person you deserve it
and
Again, I'm just sorry if I snapped because don't be sorry. It's all good under the water
I kind of came on strong as well that it's all good. Can I have a it's all good
I have a virtual hug Teresa is a big virtual hug. I am right now. Okay, give me one right now
I love you too. I do time anytime Teresa and I like really I'll make up. I'll make more of an effort to
Make sure the communications open
I'm gonna put my number in the back chat for you if you want to take me down my private number and then
No privately DM me on our private messages. Okay. I'll do it on discord. Okay. Yeah, whenever whenever you can because I know
You've got a busy thing
But why not just all vice the same thing with via like just like, you know what?
Just anytime, okay
Stop talking about each other and just move on
I'm trying but it's like every time I look her things titled after me and then maybe I titled mine after her and stuff like that
but it's like
You know, it's just it's going to hit for cat. I'm trying to like I've been telling her from the beginning
I'm like you're letting too many people get involved in our relationship and it's like too many people in her ear about it and then she's too
willing to listen to everybody else and then it's like and I was
You know, I don't know now she's saying that I used her or whatever a stepping stone
I always was promoting her. You know, I was promoting her and I was I want to promote everybody
I always said anybody can put their put their channel in my chat even Bronzeberg
I said that when we were fighting and stuff. I love promoting people. I'm here to help people
I don't I think that we're competing and we shouldn't be people in this panel verse are competing
We shouldn't be we should try to be helping each other to get popular because
I think that this can go a lot of places and so, but I love you and thank you for being here on the on the panel and
Talking to me and talking it out being willing to listen and I love you. Okay
Love you too
It was the only way I could figure out to talk to you because like I know you're busy and then the yeah
I don't know if you like see it a lot, but yeah, okay. I will let you go. Um, I got to go on
I'll do that things to do. All right. Okay. Love you. Bye bud. Love you too bud. Bye
Okay, see that I mean that's like someone that's willing to talk things out. I really like that and Teresa is a great person
She's on my traveling. It's my traveling gypsy tarot. Okay, and I'm sorry I got her
I did I did fix the the link. It's but it still doesn't go to her her channel
You're gonna say show proof hundred times when people already have okay home. It's like I don't know who you're talking about but
I will show what happened last time I was on her panel.
This is a trip kick video,
I'll just play a few minutes,
but I just want you to see what happened last,
one of the last times, not yesterday, but it was recently,
when I tried to go on her panel and talk and I came in,
I was actually had a good conversation
with her earlier on the panel when we were one on one.
We were laughing, we were joking together, it was fun.
And it just sucks that it's like,
She can't give me five minutes to talk one-on-one. She can't like really even given her chats like come on beta like
Come on like
She doesn't want to work it out obviously
Because I think it's important to work out but
Even if we were to part like decide. Hey, you know what it's just better if we part of separate ways that can be the conversation
You know it can be like you know, she says I don't want to talk to you anymore. I'm not gonna bother her again. I'll leave her alone, you know
Sometimes I do try to get people's attention, but you know with like stupid songs and stuff like that, but let's see
Let's see and Carl ignited the beat is kitty feud. So this is the heated panel face off
This is I'll just play a little bit of it because it's really annoying. It's really really really annoying
You can just see how I'm treated on her panel and stuff. So this is when I went over to her panel
recently, and this is a TripKick video,
so this is a public domain, right?
She has no problem with TripKick sharing her,
sharing her thing, and I'm willing to talk
about things rationally.
If even if I'm mad and stuff,
I'm willing to talk about things rationally,
but she won't, it's frustrating,
but I don't know what I'm supposed to expect.
So here, look, this is it.
community post I even sent him the screenshot and he was like, he's like, I don't want war with you. Like, I just want like doing my own things like he, you know, he doesn't know the rejection.
How was your birthday yesterday, Katie?
That's all right.
Happy belated candy.
Thank you.
Do you have a nice dinner or something?
No, I had a ham sandwich.
Ham sandwich?
It could be good.
I guess, I don't know.
Well, it was your birthday ham sandwich.
That's what's good for you.
I ate your biscuit.
Hi, Chris.
Thank you, Chris.
No, I'm serious.
I do.
My new hobby is porn bombing old people with Alex Mayer's porn.
I think it's hilarious.
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
AI song and you were on my panel last night acting like everything was okay
I was putting it nice to you and you know what when I came in your fucking chat you fucking banned me
You're a pussy cuz you don't want people to know the truth never did never did were restreaming me. Why are you lying?
I wasn't receiving her. I mean your viewers. Oh, um, I never restream her
It just fucking shows right there.
Sorry, sorry, I'm fine.
Get the link, get the link.
Get a photo.
Be scared.
All he's got to do is make all music about it.
Yeah, take the link.
Tell you basically all I need to know about it.
Watch this.
Take J-Dog to the side, and you'll be able to be friends.
Watch how many kids.
This is how I'm treated when there's five people on the panel.
He's a fucking weak link, and you know what?
I don't want people that play like that.
I'm sorry.
I mean, I should have listened a long time ago to it,
like some strong-minded people.
I don't want it.
I really don't want it.
I think you're a fucking pussy. I really do
Okay guys do that when they're gonna fight to get their hands
He's bashing up.
You fake motherfucker, you fake ass motherfucking manipulating people.
Now you're getting J-Dog and Alice to go against Peter.
The fuck is wrong with you, fam?
Did you just allow, did you hear what J-Dog just said about?
Shut your shit down.
Hold on, once I can, Bronzeberg.
Let him talk.
No, I want to ask you this.
Why did you just let J-Dog say that Sam had hurt his dog?
And you said nothing.
No idea about any of that. I wasn't here. You don't you can't be like don't why are you making so J dog can say whatever
The fuck he wants and when people say something as simple as hey get a litter box for your cat
You have a shit fit and you have a tantrum about it
We'd be saying we'd be saying oh, we're gonna strike you for harassment. We're gonna take on your channel, bubba
You're you know, you're good. Sweet. Okay, sweet. He did that. What were you doing?
Even in the chat
You lie all the time you literally said you weren't restraining me
Wait, did you re-streaming yesterday or not?
I'm re-streaming you.
You weren't?
Look at my, you guys, everybody go, I'm looking at my community page and post and tell me,
does it look like he was re-streaming, are you lying?
I don't like liars.
A few seconds, but a few seconds?
Okay, so you were re-streaming me.
Why?
You don't have anything of your own?
Okay, so you were re-streaming me.
No.
Oh my god.
He started to be screaming at food in my queue.
So it came up for two seconds.
You sent Mason over here too.
Like, you know Mason is like, yes, you did.
He said it.
He was telling us that you did.
No, for years, guys.
He sent me here.
Yes, he did.
And I was like, I don't know.
And he was like, he just told me to come here.
He said it over and over.
Why would Mason lie about that, though, Psycho?
Well, Mason's a little bit confused. I'm sorry.
Oh, really? Now you're going to fuck you up?
Okay, well, he's confused with everyone else.
Now you're going to put him down.
Let me know what he's confused with.
You let him up there and you let him get exploited
by people that you shouldn't really let.
Like, please, I'm protecting him, please.
You're not protecting him, you fucking liar.
You don't protect him.
You had him come over to beat his ass.
You people are fucking clowns and puppets.
You have no mercy.
You have no morals. You have no ethics.
All of your rules, you're all of your rules of motion.
you scumbag piece of shit the fuck you doing having him come over to beat his
chest so we can get exploited like that you dumb and then you sit up there
re-streaming and beat his shit and then you sit up there to have in the
videos a trip cake shut the fuck up bitch I'm talking
shut the fuck up bitch shut the fuck up bitch I'm talking
fuck you anyway like I said you can't stop sitting up there re-streaming
beat his shit every single time a trip cake comes out with a video you want to sit
up there and review beat him you fake motherfucker
Fuck out of here. You fake as fuck bro. You fake motherfucker
I'm gonna sit up there and see you talk about Vita all fucking day
And then you want to sit up there and talk about why we can't be cool because you be streamer of shit
Oh, please
You fake motherfucker cry cry after the stream is over make a stream instead of being cry about how everybody hates you
You fake as fuck you turn on all your fucking friends and then when I sit up there and talk about why people hate you
Because of the dumb shit you do you know bum ass little a.i.s songs you make
Dumb bitch. You don't think I've been watching you girl
Fake motherfucker
Don't what excuse me about your channel. Okay. What about my channel? At least I'm not fake. Okay. Oh, talk about my channel
Talk about my channel
My channel, is that the best you can do, psyche?
Hey, J-Dogs, Robert is nipples listening to this.
Like, you just giving me more fucking cred, bro.
You want to talk about my channel.
At least I'm not fake, though.
Like, you.
What does that even mean?
You're fake.
You're a fake ass motherfucker.
You filter all of your fucking chat.
You actually, all I came in there and I was like,
he's lying.
You banned me.
You filter your chat, look at, look at, look at, look at like a little child, nodding your head, like, you know, whatever.
Hey, don't get mad when people are giving you reality, all right?
Yeah, you're sitting here joking about biscuits all day, I make a, what, what biscuit?
Oh, making jokes about biscuits, what's it to you? That song was created 12 years ago, it has nothing to do with you.
Yeah, I've heard of a parody, didn't you?
But you made a jist song about biscuits.
But you made an old and tired jist song because we just sat there talking about biscuits.
Some people say that I off my ex is a parody, right?
You look ridiculous.
You look dumb as fuck, bro.
Crying over a fucking biscuit song.
They made a fucking diss track
on that AI bullshit app you was using, bro.
You think you so big and bad, Saiki, you a pussy.
And you know that.
There's only thing you do is make AI songs
every time you get dissed on.
And you know that.
Now you wanna talk about my channel.
But you know what?
I don't give a fuck if you have more stuff.
You know I'm better than you.
Yeah, we can't be biscuits, you guys.
All of a sudden, biscuits is all about him.
It's not.
No, the song was made that fucking singers the way they made that song 12 years ago. You're a delusional
Criminals sitting up there and you let them fucking suck your dick and you say
I don't see any criminals on my fucking panel.
What were you saying?
What did I say about you?
Or say, oh, Carmen's going to get you.
Yeah, it is.
Is that something bad?
When you hurt people and you fucking do shit,
you are going to get your karma.
It's not about the biscuit and any of that.
It's about his associations and how he sits there
and obsesses about what the fuck I do.
You restream me yesterday.
You lied about it.
When I talked to you about the behind the scene,
I didn't do it.
You pick it on your panel.
You go live.
And you start talking about me.
Yeah, guys, they're not trying to, like, use the biscuits on me, right?
Not trying to.
It's right there.
It's not trying to, right?
You had me on shared screen restricting me.
It's not about me, right?
It's not about me.
talking about we're not talking this is not a celebrity are you delusional
yes this is a fucking stupid panel really delusional and yeah you're like way above
your head you guys hear me talking at all
i'm the bad guy psyche me i'm the bad guy everybody hates me but then
Are you?
You're insane.
You got nervous suddenly.
Is that why you message me and you're like,
what's the people like, watch me?
Hate me?
What do you hate?
Like, what?
Why do you care about that stuff?
And why are you taking it out on me?
Because it's a talk.
Fuck you and you're a fucking stupid, like, mod J-Dog.
Yeah, what's it about J-Dog?
I don't know.
Oops, hold on.
But that's just an example of how
I'm treated on the show, on her show.
When it's, do you see?
Do you see what's, guys, that's just bullying.
That's just bullying, right?
Do you think I want to go on a show
with like five people again against me?
Could you hear a word I said?
My microphone is low, first of all.
Hers is like all the way up, his is all the way up,
screaming at me, like just slanderous,
like just disgusting, disgusting.
Ugh, I don't know, guys.
So what is she still on does she want to do one-on-one yet? I mean her she still needs to posse behind her I
Don't know I was
Yeah, I just talked to Teresa one-on-one. It went really well, you know, she doesn't want it to heal
She wants it to go on forever, right so she can have something to talk about I guess
I don't know. She's over there talking about me all day
Whatever
Oh
God just misrepresented unable to defend myself
That's what she wants
Jamie can you come up here? I'll do one. I'm gonna do one on one with Jamie
Kaz I
Think some of this stuff needs to be discussed with this other other situation with that that ham sandwich girl on the panel
Ms. Ham sandwich 2025
Cusing me of treat. Why whatever you want to talk about we don't have to talk about that if you don't want to why cuz you came up before
But you it's okay. You don't want to know my it's fine. I
Always like to talk to you. Yeah
This ham sandwich girl saying that I doxxed her full information that I made fun of like a six-year-old
That died in a fire or something like that and I don't do that shit guys. I don't make fun
And then Bita got like you know some kid like came up on our panels like I'm a kid and oh
I bet that was Psyche and then there's HIV Awakens Zero. Oh, that's Psyche. I
Don't do that shit. I mean this is just so stupid
I'm worth fighting over
She can't even talk to me for five minutes
The only thing she talks about is criticizing me
Okay
This is fucking bomb avocado toast
Hi, you're Paul Jamie
Not your fault
Thank you
I'll play by my shitty as AI songs
on time greeting every soul that comes through the door you make the chat feel
like home and then some more
Jamie you're the heart of the room lighting up the space like a rising moon
through the chaos you always stay strong that's why this is your song
page and with summer too
nobody shakes the faith that runs through you
mason might try but can't break your stride
with loyalty and love always by your side
never
And whatever, can I help it that I love Alexander?
They're like, oh, Alexander's a homophobe.
He doesn't like gay people.
He's just gonna, he's just using,
trying to get your show taking that.
Alexander and I have set up a long time at night
reading the Bible verses and stuff.
Like, he's not a bad person.
He helped me.
Days nobody else helped me.
He's always
Even when he's mad at me, I don't think he was hateful and he never did try to take my channel down or anything
And I never had a problem with Alexander
And I did something I I kick up I kicked them I kicked them off, right?
See, you know manipulate me maybe try again just taking off for good and stuff
You know, where's where's Tracy been? It's over there on that bronze chickens channel, right?
I don't know what's wrong with my camera. I love you, Alex
And what's this with, like, do I tell Vita who to be friends with?
Do I say, oh, don't be friends with Bronze Chicken anymore?
Don't be friends with Christine. Don't be friends with Sweet Pea.
Don't be friends with 2020. All these people, person,
all these people just talking the mad shit about me and her chat.
They're all in her mods, right? Am I? No.
I'm not modded. I get timed out of her chat.
She won't talk to me one-on-one.
How about here's a challenge for beta? I'm gonna issue this challenge
Can I have five minutes to talk to you one-on-one? It can be on the show. It can be on private
Can I have five minutes am I worth that to you or no? It's like I I
Wasn't worth it today
All I asked is like 10 minutes
Without me getting kicked off
Oh, it's okay Alex. I
Probably am I'm probably pretty stupid, right?
Oh, you're talking to time I
Don't know what's wrong with my camera
Jesus I think my oh what's going on?
Guys, it's oh, yeah, the word is fatigue. I'm a little bit hate fatigue right now
Do you think I like to get upset and like, you know angry and stuff and put on the fence and just call it all these names and it hurts
Especially coming from someone that I I mean I got it. I'm gonna go guys
but
You know, if you ever do when I have a nice chat
I'm totally willing to chat with you. I
Just can't take it with the other peanut gallery, right?
To make fun of me. I'm I'm a big loser, you know, I'm so bad
I don't know. I'm just a piece of trash. Yeah, I
Shows garbage
I can message her. Yeah, but she's not gonna reply
Yeah, Alex, it's just it's hard it's hard
you know. I'm crying about it, right? Like I said, I haven't cried since my father passed away
and then I cried, you know, when I sang an Elton John song like on his anniversary of his passing
and stuff. That's, that's, that's when I cried. So whenever you're saying I'm crying about it,
I'm not crying about it. This is just, this is, I'm a little bit sad because in the bottom of
I can't be like
Just to need me to look like a fool and I
Don't know if it's worth it anymore. She she can't give me five minutes
Why do I have to like give it I
Don't know I don't think it it man. She couldn't give me five minutes
She can give me a minute one minute. She couldn't say she couldn't say come for one minute
You know, all she said is, oh, well, that's against the rules because, uh, you know, it's against the regulations or something.
I don't know what she was talking about.
I thought she makes the rules, but so she's decided to make the rule that I can't talk about anything or I can't talk to her, right?
She was, I never blocked her in my chat.
Hmm.
Yeah, I'll read Psalms night Psalm 91. Let me see
Okay, whoever dwells in the shelter of the Most High will rest in the shadow of the Almighty I will say of the Lord
He is my refuge and my fortress, my God, in whom I trust.
Surely he will save you from the foul or snare, from the deadly pestilence.
He will cover you with his feathers and under his wings you will find refuge.
Oh please not a bird. Please not a bird. I'm just kidding.
His faithfulness will be your shield and rampart.
You will not fear the tear of night, nor the arrow that flies by day, nor the pestilence
that stalks in the darkness, nor the plague that destroys at midday.
A thousand may fall at your side, ten thousand at your right hand, but it will not come near you.
You will only observe with your eyes and see the punishment of the wicked.
If you say, the Lord is my refuge, and you make the most higher dwelling, no harm will overtake you, no disaster will come near your tent, for he will command the angels concerning you to guard you in all your ways.
They will lift you up in their hands so that you will not strike your foot against the stone.
You will tread on the lion and the cobra. You will trample the great lion and the serpent.
Because he loves me, says the Lord, I will rescue him. I will protect him.
You hear me now? I'm sorry. I have my microphone fell. I'm going to read it again.
Lord is my shepherd. I lack nothing. He makes me lie down in green pastures.
He leads me beside quiet waters. He refreshes my soul. He guides me along the right path
for his name's safe. Even though I walk through the darkest valley, I will fear no evil.
For you are with me. You're rod in your staff. They comfort me.
You prepare a table before me in the presence of my enemies, you anoint my head with oil,
a cup of reflows, surely your goodness and love will follow me all the days of my life
and I will dwell in the house of the Lord forever.
You know what, Bita?
You're a coward.
You're a pure coward.
You couldn't talk to me for five, ten minutes, one-on-one?
Cowardly.
What do you think?
I'm going to win the debate?
I'm not even there to debate you.
I'm there to say I love you and, like, can we work through this, but no.
You're a coward.
Okay?
You're afraid of me
And I'm not one to be afraid of because I would never harm anybody
Even my worst enemy
So thank you guys for being here
Yeah, she's a coward. What do you think RG? What being deep RG could she give me 10 minutes one-on-one coward?
Coward I need I need Eldo up there. I need Eldo. I need Christine. I need
Five people up there so they can yell at me and talk me down
And I can't say a word and they can just call me stupid and it you know piece of trash, right?
You didn't hear any of this today
Well, were you in her chat?
Yeah, I tried to do one-on-one. I said hey, I have conditions. I
Wanted to talk to you one-on-one and
I don't want to be clapped when I'm in the middle of talking to you
And she said, conditions, oh my god, you have conditions?
Was that too much to ask?
I don't think it was.
I don't know, I do see you in her chat a lot,
but I don't know, I was too distracted.
I'm sorry if I didn't mean to accuse you of being in her
chat, I mean, you can be in her, anyone can be.
Gosh, I never had a problem with anybody in her chat.
It's just as long as they are not attacking me.
You know, I don't have a problem with people.
But when they attack me for no reason, hey, CD.
I'm sorry. Hold on. I'm going to fix my camera.
There I am. There I am.
Yeah, and BG, you're a huge humongous douchebag.
I never want to, not Nuhu, I'm talking about BG, the guy with the raider stuff. He's a douchebag.
I coach him.
You didn't see what happened tonight?
Well, I went over there and she was talking about me and then that she got like someone some little some little kid tried to get on
Panel they said that I sent the kid or whatever
There's HIV awakens tarot. Oh, I bet that's psyche
You know
I'm in the Bates kitty gang BKG it's the Bates kitty gang
That's my that's my actual last name, you know put some respect on it Bates kitty gang
I never said for Bita it always said for me because I love my family more than anybody and so
Yeah
It's Lenore
My family fates kitty gang
So anyone else went oh, I don't know what my fuck is wrong with my camera. Oh god. I
Don't know guys
Tony the conductor is lame
Absolutely lame. He's wasting
Grandfather granddaughters time. It's an any grandfather out promising some free scrap metal. I
Heard outside grandpa. What are we doing here? He's oh, we got we're getting some free scrap metal to break in people's hearts, right?
Didn't break my heart and actually they're really nice people that are coming looking for scrap metal
Have no problem with those people
You don't think she's a person. She's yeah
Yeah, she's turned to I don't know what she's turned into doesn't never pay for one pizza
Never pay for one pizza. Yeah, Alex has sent something to my house. He sent me a delicious dinner
He sent me a big crab boil
Okay, that's what Alex sent to my house. He did send something to my house. He sent me dinner one night paid for
That's a real friend, okay
I'm gonna play one more song
Then I'll leave
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I would know. I would know. Yeah, you do. You have to fill out a whole thing. Okay.
Well, anyway, but I had to get privacy, something or whatever for playing that song. So,
but it's worth it. It's worth it. Okay, guys, I love you. You know,
I'll be back later.
They docks, they slander, they gaslight, they disrupt.
But what if you had the ultimate guide to shut them down?
Introducing Trollopedia, your field manual to decode, expose, and outsmart internet trolls.
From classic tactics like love bombing to modern swarm attacks, Trollopedia breaks it all down.
Know the playbook, flip the script, take back your power. Trollopedia.